bittank.club 2018-02-08

# BITTANK LIMITED mining the easy way!

## Privacy Policy

**BitTank.club** is committed to a proactive, pro-user Privacy Policy. Your privacy and security are extremely important to us. 

##### INTRODUCTION

This privacy statement describes privacy aspects specific to the demowebsite.com web site. We respect and actively protect the privacy of those who visit and use demowebsite.com. To demonstrate our integrity and commitment to fair information practices, we have adopted leading industry privacy guidelines.   

##### 1\. CONFIDENTIALITY

**BitTank.club does not share, sell, lease, loan, rent, trade or disclose any personal information collected in the use of this Site or the creation of your User Account**.

All financial data, membership information, e-mail addresses, and any other personally identifying information are considered confidential and held in the strictest confidence. Because we maintain bank-like security standards, only specially trained and authorized employees within our own company are allowed access to any client particulars; such as names, addresses or e-mail addresses. 

##### 2\. ELECTRONIC COOKIE TECHNOLOGY

**In general, when you visit our Web site and access information you remain anonymous.** BitTank.club does not use third-party tracking systems that may assign their own cookies to you. 

> **Visitors to this Web site:** demowebsite.com (like almost all web sites) may place certain information (called "cookies") on your computer. These cookies do not track individual information. We may also use cookies when you register for one of our web programs or future promotions. BitTank.club does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in the cookie.     
>  **Registered Account Holders:** If you are a registered account holder at BitTank.club, you may receive a cookie when you sign-in. This cookie is maintained by your browser and contains your unique identifier. Cookies may be used to authenticate your identity, protect your account and facilitate your access to highly secure areas of the Site that are strictly limited to registered, active account holders. 

##### 3\. PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

BitTank.club collects no personally identifying information about you except when you knowingly and specifically submit this information for a special purpose. 

##### 4\. E-MAIL LISTS

BitTank.club may maintain e-mail lists and newsletters to enlighten and inform our users, clients and the media about our services, and/or announce upcoming news and special events. As a user or visitor to the Site, you will be included only if you sign up for such lists. 

##### 5\. CHOICE/OPT OUT

You have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and any of our partners at the point where we request information from you. On any page of this Site where you may be asked to provide personal identifying information (such as name or e-mail address) you will also be asked whether you wish to receive further communications from BitTank.club regarding our products and services. We give you the opportunity to choose not to receive materials from us. If you sign up for an electronic newsletter or e-mail list, each message will include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from that list. 

##### 6\. MINORS

Because of the financial nature of our business, this Site is not designed to appeal to children under 18 years of age. BitTank.club does not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from minors and children; and they are prohibited from using our Site and Services. 

##### 7\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Any changes or updates to this privacy statement will be effective immediately upon posting to this site. If we plan to make significant changes to any of our privacy policies or practices with respect to how we use personally identifiable information, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy before they take effect. Your continued use of this Web site will demonstrate your acceptance of the terms specified by this Privacy Policy. 

##### 8\. YOUR CONSENT

Except where we may be legally required to disclose certain information to comply with a legal process; no information relating to your use of this Site will be disclosed to an outside party without your express consent. 

##### 9\. CONTACTING US

Additional questions or concerns regarding the privacy practices of BitTank.club should be addressed to contact@BitTank.club
